welcome to
Oasis see what happened after the war
here gives me hope for the rebuilding of
my
country analyzing location hot dry
unpleasant ideal for
hamsters juson Fox minister of
engineering has a certain ring to it
this place is a bit Posh for
me if only the world could see the
Wonders that science has
built this is now my home as much as any
other I'm getting cooked alive in
here pretty place be ashamed have to
kill someone here
so what are we doing here boss I need to
pay a visit to a
friend H this place is to my
liking the vishar corporation would love
to have a presence
here a city run by scientists
smart you wouldn't believe all the
science that gets done here
what a fascinating place can science
alone unlock the path to enlightenment